<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Isaac Zhou</title>
    <link>https://www.isaaczhou.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Isaac Zhou</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.isaaczhou.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/intro-to-neural-networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/intro-to-neural-networks/</guid>
      <description> What is a Deep Neural Network    A neural network is a machine learning algorithm that can be trained using input data, e.g. camera images or sensor readings, and generate output like what&amp;rsquo;s steering angle the car should take or how fast it should go The idea is that the neural network learns from observing the world, without being taught anything specific beforehand A deep neural network is just a term that describes a huge multi-layer neural network with many hidden layers Deep learning is using deep neural networks to sovle problems and it&amp;rsquo;s becoming increasingly important for self-driving cars  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing Hugo blog in Org</title>
      <link>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/hugo-blog-in-org/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/hugo-blog-in-org/</guid>
      <description>First Heading with the post  This post will be exported as content/posts/hugo-blog-in-org.md Its title will be &amp;ldquo;Hugo Blog in Org&amp;rdquo; It will have hugo and org tags and emacs as category The menu item weight and post weight are auto-calculated The menu item identifier is auto-set the lastmod property in the front-matter is set automatically to the time of expoert  A sub-heading under that heading  It&amp;rsquo;s draft state will be marked as true as the subtree has the todo state set to TODO</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Series Analysis in Python</title>
      <link>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/time-series-analysis-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/time-series-analysis-python/</guid>
      <description>From stock prices to climate data, time series data are found in a wide variety of domains, and being able to effectively work with such data is an increasingly important skill for data scientists. I will demonstrate how to conduct time series analysis in Python in following order:
 Introduction to time series Typical time series models  Autoregresive Moving Average Cointegration  Along the way, I will show how to estimate, forecast, and simulate these models using statistical libraries in Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Crash Course</title>
      <link>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/markdown/</guid>
      <description>To write headings use #
For example, # Heading 1 will generate
Heading 1 Similarly, the rest can be generated
Heading 2 Heading 3 Heading 4 Heading 5 Heading 6 For text decoration This text is italicized, using _word_
This text is string, using **word**
This text is strikethrough, using ~~word~~
Horizontal Rules
can be done with ___ or ***
Blockquotes
 This is a quote
 Links can be done as this [Isaac Zhou](https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build a Chatbot in Python</title>
      <link>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/chatbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/chatbot/</guid>
      <description> How to build a Chatbot in Python </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>i3 Window Management</title>
      <link>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/i3-window-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/i3-window-manager/</guid>
      <description>I just started using i3 window manager and I love it. This will be the window manager for all of my Linux distros (Xubuntu and Manjaro). Here are some basics
Fundamentals Installations  Install on Ubuntu  sudo apt-get install i3   Login  Choose i3 as login   Generate config file   I choose the super key/Windows key for the modifier key
Get Started  open a terminal use Mod Enter find a program to open use Mod D to open a buffer (D menu) and enter the program i3 can also open a GUI folder  Mod D to trigger the D menu xdg-open /path e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>D3 in Hugo</title>
      <link>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/d3-visualization-embedded-in-jupyter-notebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/d3-visualization-embedded-in-jupyter-notebook/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Org-Mode Capabilities</title>
      <link>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/all-about-org-mode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/all-about-org-mode/</guid>
      <description>One of the reasons my marriage with Jupyter didn&amp;rsquo;t hold was the beautiful and sexy org-mode. I was totally blown away the first time I saw it. Just like emacs is more than a text editor; org-mode is much more than a note-taking, spreadsheet, task tracker, planner, literate programming code editor (Oh Yeah!!!)&amp;hellip; I guess the proper definition for org-mode is really an Emacs subsystem.
The Almighty Org-Mode The org-mode was first introduced to the world in 2008 at this Google Talk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experiencing and Enjoying Emacs</title>
      <link>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/emacs-history-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/emacs-history-setup/</guid>
      <description>A little bit about my background Actually I learnt about emacs really long time ago. It was around 2003~2004, when I was still a college student majoring in Computer Science back in China. I majored in a top notch major in a top tier engineering school in China. However, I was not in love of it. The environment was really choking back then and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t see my future there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fancy App 1</title>
      <link>https://www.isaaczhou.com/itemized/item1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.isaaczhou.com/itemized/item1/</guid>
      <description> App 1 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fancy App 2</title>
      <link>https://www.isaaczhou.com/itemized/item2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.isaaczhou.com/itemized/item2/</guid>
      <description> App 2 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fancy App 3</title>
      <link>https://www.isaaczhou.com/itemized/item3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.isaaczhou.com/itemized/item3/</guid>
      <description> App 3 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fancy App 4</title>
      <link>https://www.isaaczhou.com/itemized/item4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.isaaczhou.com/itemized/item4/</guid>
      <description> App 4 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.isaaczhou.com/post/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-1-install-hugo&#34;&gt;Step 1. Install Hugo&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go to &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/spf13/hugo/releases&#34;&gt;hugo releases&lt;/a&gt; and download the
appropriate version for your os and architecture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More complete instructions are available at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.isaaczhou.com/overview/installing/&#34;&gt;installing hugo&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>